Guide to the Susan A. Henry papers, 1998-2010.
Henry, Susan A. papers, 1998-2010
- Series VIII. Subject Files
  - Animal Science - Small Farms, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Animal Science - Test Day Model, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - James A. Hegen vs. Cornell University, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - AEM (Applied Economics and Management)- Agriculture Finance Management, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AEM - Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AEM - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AEM - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AEM - Extension and Outreach, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - AEM - Food Brand Lab, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - AEM - Local Government Program, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AEM - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AEM -Poverty, Inequality, & Development Initiative, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AEM - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AEM/UGBP-Admissions, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AEM/UGBP - Advisory Council, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AEM/UGBP - Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AEM/UGBP - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - AEM/UGBP - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - AEM/UGBP - Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - AEM - Department Chair, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - AEM - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Business Education, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - AEM - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - AEM - AACSB, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - AEM - AACSB, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - BEE (Biological and Environmental Engineering)- Aquaculture, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - BEE - Biomedical Engineering, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - BEE -Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - BEE - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - BEE - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - BEE - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - BEE - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - BEE - Facilities, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - BEE - History, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - BEE - Local Roads, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - BEE -Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - BEE - Dave Pimental, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - BEE - Dave Pimental, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - BEE - Salary Improvement Program, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - BEE -Sun Grant Initiative, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - BSCB (Biological Statistics and Computational Biology) -Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - BSCB -Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - BSCB -Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - BSCB -Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - BSCB -MTBI, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - BSCB -Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - BSCB -Statistical Sciences, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - BSCB -Transitions Steering Committee, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Communication - Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Communication - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Communication - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Communication - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Communication - The Past,,,as prologue to the future, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Communication - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Communication - Forensics, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Communication - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences- Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Development/Fund Raising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Nutrient Analysis Lab, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Crop and Soil Sciences - Cornell Waste Management, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Development Sociology - Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Development Sociology - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Development Sociology - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Development Sociology - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Development Sociology - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Development Sociology - CFAP, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Development Sociology - Extension and Outreach, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Rural Sociology - Future of American Agriculture, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Rural Sociology - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Advisory Council, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Director Search, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Development Sociology - Farmworker Program Transition, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Development Sociology - Unit Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture Labor Markets in New York State, May 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - EAS (Earth and Atmospheric Sciences)- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - EAS - Co-Location Study, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - EAS - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - EAS- Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - EAS- Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - EAS - Department Merger, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - EAS - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - EAS - Extension and Outreach, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - EAS - Lead Dean Agreement, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - EAS - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - EEB (Ecology and Evolutionary Biology)- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - EEB - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - EEB- Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - EEB- Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Education - Accreditation, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Education - Ag In the Classroom, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Education - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Education - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Education - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Education - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Education - Higher Education Opportunity Act, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Education - History of Agreement for Education, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Education - Mathematics Education program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Education - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Education - New York State for Rural Schools Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Education - Rural Schools Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Education - SAC Special Advisory Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Education - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Education - Report to the Special Advisory Council, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Education - Faculty Committee Department Review, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Education - Joint Study Communication & Education, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Education - Background material Joint Communication and Education Self Study, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Entomology - American Entomological Institute, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Entomology - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Entomology- Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Entomology - Department Merger, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Entomology- Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Entomology - External Review, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Entomology - Development and Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Entomology - Dyce Lab, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Entomology - Extension and Outreach, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Entomology - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Food Science- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Food Science- Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Food Science- Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Food Science- Dairy Operations, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Food Science - Department Merger, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Food Science- Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Food Science - Development and Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Food Science - Extension and Outreach, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Food Science - Cornell Institute of Food Science, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Food Science -ICET (Institute for Comparative and Environmental Toxicology), July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Food Science - Ludwig Institute for Cancer Research, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Food Science- Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Food Science- Onion Controversy, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Food Science- Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Horticulture- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Horticulture - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Horticulture - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Horticulture - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Horticulture -Dilmun Hill, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Horticulture - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Horticulture - Pesticide Management Education Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Horticulture - Turfgrass, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Horticulture - Leslie Weston, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Landscape Architecture - Accreditation, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Landscape Architecture- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Landscape Architecture - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Landscape Architecture - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Landscape Architecture- Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Landscape Architecture - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Microbiology - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Microbiology - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Microbiology - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Microbiology - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - MBG (Molecular Biology and Genetics)- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - MBG - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - MBG - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - MBG - Development/Fund Raising, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - MBG - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Natural Resources- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Natural Resources - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Natural Resources - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Natural Resources - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Natural Resources - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Natural Resources - Hudson River Estuary, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Natural Resources - Arnot Forest, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Natural Resources - Biological Field Station, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Natural Resources - Maple Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Natural Resources -Uihlein Research Station, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Neurobiology and Behavior- Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Neurobiology and Behavior - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Neurobiology and Behavior - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Neurobiology and Behavior - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Animal Facilities, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Strategic Plan, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Nutritional Sciences -Governance, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Name Changes, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Nutritional Sciences - Cornell Institute for Nutritional Genomics, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Plant Biology - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Plant Biology - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Plant Biology - Esbaran Amazon Station, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Plant Biology - Punta Cana lab, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Plant Breeding - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Plant Breeding - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Plant Breeding - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Plant Breeding - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Plant Breeding - New York Seed Improvement Project, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Plant Pathology - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Plant Pathology - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Plant Pathology - Curriculum, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Plant Pathology - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Plant Pathology - Guterman Lab - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Biological Sciences Reorganization, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Geneva - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Geneva - Director, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Geneva - Director Search, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Geneva - Name Change, 1972-1991 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Geneva - White Paper Task Force, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Geneva - Enology and Viticulture Program, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Geneva - Facilities, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - CAFTP (Cornell Agriculture and Food Technology Park) - Budget, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - CAFTP - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - CAFTP -Director, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - CAFTP -Economic Development, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - CAFTP -International Documents, July 2001 - July 2010 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - CAFTP - Real Estate (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lake Erie Regional Grape, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lake Erie Regional Grape, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lake Erie Regional Grape, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lake Erie Regional Grape and Extension Lab, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Geneva - New York Crops Research Facility, 1993-2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Geneva - New York State Food Venture, 2001-2011 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Geneva - Northeast Region IR 4 Program, 1993-2010 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Geneva -Seed Testing Lab, 1993-2010 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Geneva - Vinification and Brewing Gala, 2000-2008 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Geneva - Hudson Valley Laboratory, 1964-2009 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Department of Food Science and Technology-Organizational Review and Intervention, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Environmental and Natural Resources Planning Council, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Environmental and Natural Resources Planning Council, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Environmental and Natural Resources Planning Council, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Associates - David Alexander, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Associates - Hillary Rodham Clinton, 2002-2008 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Associates - Hillary Rodham Clinton Farmbill, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Associates - Lee Telega & Hillary Rodham Clinton Farmbill, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Food System Health Task Force, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - GMO (Genetically Modified Organisms) Task Force, 2003-2008 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Land Grant Mission Task Force, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Plant Science Task Force Summary, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Plant Science Task Force, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Social Sciences Task Force, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Biology Task Force, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Apple Industry Task Force, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - CALS Policy Committee, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - CALS Senate Ad-Hoc Policy Committee, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Barbara McClintock's Ear of Corn, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Susan Henry and Barbara McClintock Notes (Volume I)